http://www.keela.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Holiday Closure Dates
Covid-19 Update
Skip to content
1.0 Introduction
Keela is committed to protecting your personal privacy. This Privacy Notice is to help you understand how we collect and use information about you.We hope that the contents of this Privacy Notice will answer your questions but if not please contact us. Contact details can be found in the “Any questions for us” section at the end.
2.0 Who We Are
Keela International, also known as KeelaWhen you are using the Keela website, Keela is the data controller and as controller we are responsible for, and control the processing of, your personal data.Our website address is: https://www.keelaoutdoors.com
3.0 The Legal Basis For Collecting And Processing Your Personal Data
The law on data protection sets out a number of different reasons for which a company may collect and process your personal data, including:
Contractual NecessityIn certain circumstances, we need your personal data to comply with our contractual obligations. For example:-
If you order an item from us for home delivery, we’ll collect your address details and pass them to our courierLegitimate InterestsIn certain situations, we require your data to pursue our legitimate interests in a way which might reasonably be expected as part of running our business and which does not materially impact your rights, freedom or interests. For example:-
– We may use your purchase history to send you or make available personalised offers– We may also combine the shopping history of many customers to identify trends and ensure we can keep up with demand, or develop new products/services– We may use your address details to send you direct marketing information by post, telling you about products and services that we think might interest you
Legal ComplianceWe may process your personal data if we have a legal obligation to do so, for example to co-operate with an investigation pursuant to a court order.
ConsentIn specific situations, we can collect and process your data with your consent. For example, when you tick a box in order to receive email newsletters.When collecting your personal data, we’ll always make clear to you which data is necessary in connection with a particular service.
4.0 When Do We Collect Your Personal Data?
– When you create an account with us– When you visit our website, and use your account to buy products and services, or redeem vouchers on the phone, or online– When you make an online purchase and check out as a guest (in which case we just collect transaction-based data)– When you purchase a product or service by phone or by email but don’t have (or don’t use) an account– When you engage with us on social media– When you contact us by any means with queries, complaints etc.– When you ask one of our team to email you information about a product– When you enter prize draws or competitions– When you book any kind of appointment with us or book to attend an event– When you choose to complete any surveys we send you– When you comment on or review our products and services– Any individual may access personal data related to them, including opinions. So if your comment or review includes information about the member of our team who helped you, it may be passed on to them if requested– When you’ve given a third party permission to share with us the information they hold about you– When you leave a comment (including images)
5.0 What Sort Of Personal Data Do We Collect?
– If you have a web account with us: your name, gender, date of birth, billing/delivery address, orders and receipts, email and telephone number. For your security, we’ll also keep an encrypted record of your login password.– Details of your interactions with us via phone or email or online. For example, we record notes from our conversations with you, details of any complaints or comments you make, details of purchases you made, items viewed or added to your basket, wish list choices, voucher redemptions, web pages you visit and how and when you contact us.– Details of your visits to our websites and which site you came from to ours– Personal details which help us to recommend items of interest. For example, you might tell us your clothing size, which we then may use to guide our suggested items.– Your comments and product reviews– To deliver the best possible web experience, we collect technical information about your internet connection and browser as well as the country and telephone code where your computer is located, the web pages viewed during your visit, the advertisements you clicked on, and any search terms you entered.– Your social media username, if you interact with us through those channels, to help us respond to your comments, questions or feedback– Information gathered by the use of cookies in your web browser – please see our Cookies Policy– When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.– If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.– If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.– Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
6.0 How And Why We Use Your Personal Data?
Our aim is to give you the best possible customer experience. One way we can achieve this is by combining the data we have about so that we can offer you promotions, products and services that are likely to interest you.The data privacy law allows this as part of our legitimate interest in understanding our customers so that we can provide them the highest level of service.Of course, if you wish to change how we use your data, you’ll find details in the ‘What are your rights over your personal data?’ section below.However, please remember that if you choose not to share your personal data with us, or refuse certain contact permissions, we might not be able to provide some services you’ve asked for. For example, if you’ve asked us to let you know when an item comes back into stock, we can’t do that if you’ve withdrawn your general consent to hear from us.
Here’s how we’ll use your personal data and why:-– To process any orders that you make by using our website, by phone or email. If we don’t collect your personal data we won’t be able to process your order and we won’t be able to comply with our legal obligations. For example, we may need to pass your details to a third party to supply or deliver the product that you ordered, and we may keep your details for a reasonable period afterwards in order to fulfil any contractual obligations such as refunds, guarantees and so on.– To respond to your queries, refund requests and complaints. Handling the information you sent enables us to respond. We may also keep a record of these to inform any future communication with us and to demonstrate how we communicated with you throughout. We do this on the basis of our contractual obligations to you, our legal obligations and our legitimate interests in providing you with the best service and understanding how we can improve our service based on your experience.– To protect our business and your account from fraud and other illegal activities. This includes using your personal data to maintain, update and safeguard your account. We’ll also monitor your browsing activity with us to quickly identify and resolve any problems and protect the integrity of our websites. We’ll do all of this as part of our legitimate interest.– To process payments and to prevent fraudulent transactions. We do this on the basis of our legitimate business interests. This also helps to protect our customers from fraud.– If we discover any criminal activity or alleged criminal activity through fraud monitoring and suspicious transaction monitoring, we will process this data for the purposes of preventing or detecting unlawful acts. We aim is to protect the individuals we interact with from criminal activities.– With your consent, we will use your personal data, preferences and details of your transactions to keep you informed by email, web, text and telephone about relevant products and services including tailored special offers, discounts, promotions, events, competitions and so on – of course, you are free to opt out of hearing from us by any of these channels at any time– To send you relevant, personalised communications by post in relation to updates, offers, services and products. We’ll do this on the basis of our legitimate business interest – of course, you are free to opt out of hearing from us by post at any time.– To send you communications required by law or which are necessary to inform you about our changes to the services we provide you. For example, updates to this Privacy Notice, product recall notices, and legally required information relating to your orders. These service messages will not include any promotional content and do not require prior consent when sent by email or text message. If we do not use your personal data for these purposes, we would be unable to comply with our legal obligations.– To display the content that is likely to be of most interest to you on our websites, we’ll use data we hold about your favourite brands or products and so on. We do so on the basis of your consent for our website to place cookies or similar technology on your device. For example, we might display a list of items you’ve recently looked at, or offer you recommendations based on your purchase history and any other data you’ve shared with us.– To administer any of our prize draws or competitions which you enter, based on your consent given at the time of entering.– To develop, test and improve the systems, services and products we provide to you. We’ll do this on the basis of our legitimate business interests.– To comply with our contractual or legal obligations to share data with law enforcement. For example, when a court order is submitted to share data with law enforcement agencies or a court of law.– To send you survey and feedback requests to help improve our services. These messages will not include any promotional content and do not require prior consent when sent by email or text message. We have a legitimate interest to do so as this helps make our products or services more relevant to you. Of course, you are free to opt out of receiving these requests from us at any time.– To build a rich picture of who you are and what you like, and to inform our business decisions, we’ll combine data captured by Keela and by third parties (for example list of attendees at trade shows) and data from other publicly-available lists as we have described in the ‘What Sort of Personal Data do we collect?’ section above. We will do this on the basis of our legitimate business interest. For example, by combining this data, this will help us personalise your experience and decide which inspiration or content to share with you. We also use anonymised data from customer purchase histories to identify trends.
Please note that Keela does not buy lists.
7.0 Who Do We Share Your Personal Data With?
We sometimes share your personal data with trusted third parties, but only in order to fulfil contractual necessity e.g. we would share your address details with couriers so that they could deliver an item that you have bought from us.We will never share your personal data with a third party for their own purposes e.g. so that they can market their products to you.In order that your data is kept safe and that your privacy is protected we apply the following policy when sharing your data with a third party:– We provide only the information they need to perform their specific services– They may only use your data for the exact purposes we specify in our contract with them– We work closely with them to ensure that your privacy is respected and protected at all times– If we stop using their services, any of your data held by them will either be deleted or rendered anonymous– Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
8.0 How We Protect Your Personal Data
We know how much data security matters to all our customers. With this in mind we will treat your data with the utmost care and take all appropriate steps to protect it.Access to your personal data is password-protected and payment card information is secured and tokenised to ensure it is protected.We secure access to all transactional areas of our websites using ‘https’ technology.
9.0 How Long Will We Keep Your Personal Data?
Whenever we collect or process your personal data, we’ll only keep it for as long as is necessary for the purpose for which it was collected.At the end of that retention period, your data will either be deleted completely or anonymised, for example by aggregation with other data so that it can be used in a non-identifiable way for statistical analysis and business planning.
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
10.0 Where Your Personal Data May Be Processed
Sometimes we will need to share your personal data with third parties and suppliers outside the European Economic Area (EEA).For example, if you are based outside the EEA and place an order with us, we will transfer the personal data that we collect from you to our UK business where your data will be treated with care in accordance with this Privacy Notice.If you live outside the EEA we may transfer personal data that we collect from you to a third party (e.g. a courier) who is based outside the EEA so that we can fulfil our contractual obligation and deliver a product to you.If we do this, we have procedures in place to ensure your data receives the same protection as if it were being processed inside the EEA.
11.0 What Are Your Rights Over Your Personal Data?
An overview of your different rightsYou have the right to request: – Access to the personal data we hold about you, free of charge in most cases– The correction of your personal data when incorrect, out of date or incomplete– That we stop using your personal data for direct marketing (either through specific channels, or all channels)– That we stop any consent-based processing of your personal data after you withdraw that consent– Review by a Partner of any decision made based solely on automatic processing of your data (i.e. where no human has yet reviewed the outcome and criteria for the decision)– You have the right to request a copy of any information about you that Keela holds at any time, and also to have that information corrected if it is inaccurate. To ask for your information, please contact Keela, 52-53 Nasmyth Road, Glenrothes, Fife , KY6 2SD. To ask for your information to be amended, please update your online account, or contact our Sales team.– If we choose not to action your request we will explain to you the reasons for our refusal
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Your right to withdraw consent:-Whenever you have given us your consent to use your personal data, you have the right to change your mind at any time and withdraw that consent.
Where we rely on our legitimate interest:-In cases where we are processing your personal data on the basis of our legitimate interest, you can ask us to stop for reasons connected to your individual situation. We must then do so unless we believe we have a legitimate overriding reason to continue processing your personal data.
Direct marketing:-You have the right to stop the use of your personal data for direct marketing activity through all channels, or selected channels. We must always comply with your request.
Checking your identity:-To protect the confidentiality of your information, we will ask you to verify your identity before proceeding with any request you make under this Privacy Notice. If you have authorised a third party to submit a request on your behalf, we will ask them to prove they have your permission to act.
12.0 How Can You Stop The Use Of Your Personal Data For Direct Marketing?
There are several ways you can stop direct marketing communications from us:
Click the ‘unsubscribe’ link in any email communication that we send you. We will then stop sending these email communications to you.If you have an account that has “preferences” settings, log in into your account and change your preferencesWrite to Keela at 52-53 Nasmyth Road, Glenrothes, Fife , KY6 2SD.Please note that you may continue to receive communications for a short period after changing your preferences while our systems are fully updated.
13.0 Contacting The Regulator
If you feel that your data has not been handled correctly, or you are unhappy with our response to any requests you have made to us regarding the use of your personal data, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office.If you are based outside the UK, you have the right to lodge your complaint with the relevant data protection regulator in your country of residence.
14.0 Any Questions For Us?
We hope this Privacy Notice has been helpful in setting out the way we handle your personal data and your rights to control it.However, if you have any questions or concerns please write to us at Keela, 52-53 Nasmyth Road, Glenrothes, Fife , KY6 2SD.
Privacy Notice last updated 24th May 2018
Keep up to date with the latest news, special offers and newest products from Keela.
Sign up to our newsletter
Holiday Closure & Reduced Working Dates
To try and give all of our staff a break after the difficult year we have faced, we will be closed from 23rd Dec to the 4th Jan – although we will have a small team in on the 23rd and 29th Dec.
This means orders placed during this period may face delays and take longer to arrive – and any enquiries may take a bit longer to respond to, although the team will do their best to get back to you asap.
We appreciate your patience during this period – and wish you a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year!
CLOSE
Test Goes Here
CLOSE
Innovation
Innovation fabric is designed for the highest hills and tallest mountains.
Developed to be the last word in high end waterproof/breathable performance fabric, the Innovation range is most often found in combination with our System Dual Protection technology due to its ideal compatibility and usability.
A texturised nylon laminate coated with hydrophilic PU fabric; highly breathable and wickable with excellent waterproofing, Innovation 5 is used in our System Dual Protection range.
CLOSE
Ventile
Originally designed in the UK, Ventile® is densely woven from 100% cotton using the world’s finest long staple fibre.
Ventile® is not coated or laminated yet the combination of the dense weave and the swelling properties of the fibres when wet provide excellent weatherproofing.
It is an entirely natural product that offers a unique level of comfort, look and feel as well as being windproof, highly breathable, very durable and quiet.
Ventile® fabrics are used in some of the world’s finest outerwear performance garments and have military, medical and workwear applications. What’s more, they look great!
The long pedigree of the fabric goes back as far as the late 1930’s. With war looming, the British government thought that there would be a shortage of flax that was used in those days for fire hoses and water buckets. An alternative was required and research was commenced into the use of cottons, woven in such a way as to keep water in ! And it worked.
The requirements for research though changed during World War II. Britain depended upon convoys carrying vital supplies, but our Russian convoys across the Arctic Ocean were particularly susceptible to attack from submarines and long – range bombers. Home based RAF fighter escort cover was impossible because of distance.
So, Winston Churchill promoted the concept of catapulting expendable Hurricane aircraft from the decks of merchant ships to provide local cover. There was no means of landing back on the deck. The pilot had the choice of ditching the aircraft or bailing out into the sea. There was no problem in spotting the pilots who had signals and lights, but the water was so cold that life expectancy was only a few minutes. Most died from exposure.
There was an urgent need for a new, protective clothing fabric that would be comfortable in the cockpit under combat conditions and that would also keep a pilot warm and dry in the sea. After many trials, the scientists at the Shirley Institute in Manchester U.K. developed the fabric called ‘Ventile’. When made into finished garments, life expectancy in the sea was extended from a few minutes to 20 minutes and rescue was now a real possibility. 80% of anti-submarine pilots who fell into the sea now survived.
Ventile® fabrics for RAF clothing went into mass production in 1943 and the military association still remains today. Garment designs have changed over the years but you will still find Ventile® suits in modern Tornado jets with the RAF and other NATO airforces.
CLOSE
ViralOff
Polygiene started in the care segment during the fight against SARS in 2004 – while Viral-Off is particularly relevant in the current CV19 situation, it will also be a longer term solution to enhance hygiene even once the pandemic has settled down.
ViralOff is not intended to prevent disease, it is used for the protection of the treated product
Does it help against all viruses?
The active ingredient has been tested against Influenza A, BirdFlu, Norovirus and Corona (SARS) over the years, and in all cases, has achieved 99% levels of reduction.
The ISO18184:2019 is a standard test for the determination of the antiviral activity of textile products in a two-hour timespan, where it has to reduce the virus by 99%, to pass. This test uses viruses of the Influenza A strain.
How long does it last?
It is a durable and always-on treatment. For best performance and sustainability, wash less and only when needed.
CLOSE
Insect Shield
Every day, millions of people are exposed to insects that can carry malaria, Dengue fever, trypanosomiasis, fi lariasis, leishmaniasis, and other dangerous diseases.
Insect Shield’s long-lasting clothing treatment — proven to last through 70 washings on apparel and 25 washings on gear — is a vital solution for people living in harm’s way.
Lyme disease is the most commonly reported insect borne illness in the United States, and has now become one of the fastest growing epidemics to date, while Malaria is responsible for approximately one million deaths worldwide.
Insect Shield technology converts clothing and gear into long-lasting, effective and convenient insect protection.
The active ingredient in Insect Shield, permethrin, is so tightly bonded to the fabric fibers that it retains effective repellency through the expected life of the product.
Permethrin is a synthetic version of a naturally occurring repellent found in certain types of chrysanthemum plants such as the African Daisy.
The insecticide properties of chrysanthemums have been known for decades. Permethrin affects the nervous system in insects when they come in contact with it.
Permethrin is effective against a number of pesky and potentially dangerous insects such as mosquitoes, ticks, ants, flies chiggers and midges including those that can carry dangerous diseases such as malaria, dengue fever or Lyme.
CLOSE
CADS
Years of research and development into base layer fabrics has helped us to achieve Carbonised Active Dispersal System (CADS) – the ultimate wickable fabric base layer.
The specially constructed yarn network rapidly draws moisture away from the body and disperses it over a large area for fast evaporation into the surrounding atmosphere. Its super-fast wicking and high breathability rate works with the human body to keep the wearer dry and comfortable 100% of the time.Being Anti-Microbial enables it to eliminate odours being emitted from the wearer while offering a higher standard of hygiene.
Perfect for use on its own in warm weather or as part of a layering system in colder climates, CADS is the next step in performance fabrics next to the skin.
CLOSE
ADS Technology
Keela’s Active Dispersal System (ADS) is the ultimate moisture management system.
Its specially structured star yarn rapidly removes moisture away from the body, dispersing it over a large area for fast evaporation into the outside atmosphere, keeping you drier for longer.
The moisture management is inherent in the manufactured construction and cannot be washed out, ensuring it lasts the lifetime of the garment.
ADS also protects from the sun’s harmful rays and has a UV protection level of +40.
ADS works in harmony with your body, providing maximum comfort during periods of high activity outdoor sports.
Keela’s ADS garments are perfect for use worn individually in warm weather or as a base layer in conjunction with a layering system in colder environments.
ADS Thermal is the ideal thermal control layer for active use.
Constructed from our ADS star yarn fabric with an added layer of thin fleece on the inside, ADS Thermal is excellent at heat generation without the bulk of a fleece yet is highly breathable.
CLOSE
Merino
We use two different Merino mixes, a 100% Merino which has all of the natural Merino qualities, as well as an 80-20 Merino mix, which gives an increased durability.
Merino wool is a natural fibre which is produced by various species of merino sheep.
Many associate wool products to be irritable and rough against the skin, however, Merino is well known for its warmth and soft feel against the skin, and is regarded as one of the best options for use in baselayers.
What type of clothing contains Merino Wool?
Merino wool can be used for various types of clothing, due to its natural properties to insure a warm soft fit against the skin.
Similarly Merino works in the same manner as a micro-fleece as the fibre is able to trap and disperse the necessary amount of heat.
CLOSE
Primaloft
PrimaLoft is incredibly soft, lightweight and breathable with excellent water repellency so you remain dry, warm and comfortable, even under the most extreme conditions.
Ounce for ounce as warm as down, Primaloft microfibres are similar in size and shape to down, resulting in nearly equal insulating performance when dry and even better when wet.
Because its individual fibres are water repellent, Primaloft retains much of its ability to keep you warm, even when moisture has soaked through.
Primaloft Gold Active is designed to regulate your comfort level during intense activity, while offering performance without compromise in a wide range of conditions.
Similar to the structure of down with incredible softness, Primaloft is highly compressible and easy to stuff.
Its resilient fibres are quick to regain their loft to provide uncompromising insulation.
Primaloft insulation is soft and supple like down, making it an excellent choice for active outerwear.
It allows unrestricted movement and its light weight makes it comfortable for extended wear.
CLOSE
AirXtream is a specially developed 3-layer material concept.
The outer consists of a pique weave with a durable water resistant treatment laminated onto a waterproof hydrophilic membrane.
This in turn is laminated to the inner liner, which has rapid moisture wicking properties.
Airxtreme Advanced is designed to minimise the number of layers needed to insulate and protect against extreme elements.
Used as part of a layering system or alone as an outershell, the durable water repellent finish repels rain and snow while the tight weave gives excellent windproofing.
The textured brushed lining provides a comfortable insulating inner and the inherent stretch provides ease of movement.
CLOSE
AirXtream
AirXtream is a specially developed 3-layer material concept.
The outer consists of a pique weave with a durable water resistant treatment laminated onto a waterproof hydrophilic membrane.
This in turn is laminated to the inner liner, which has rapid moisture wicking properties.
AirXtream has a high percentage of stretch for added comfort while still retaining its durability. Its weatherproofing means it can be used for longer on its own when the weather turns bad and acts as the perfect mid layer in colder conditions, reducing bulk while still helping to retain insulation.
A combination of materials brought together in one performance system. The outer woven stretch component is treated with a highly durable water repellent finish and then bonded to a hydrophilic membrane.
The final component is the lining; this ‘Air Channel Matrix’ system minimizes contact with inner clothing or skin and allows for an increased air gap, helping to improve the overall performance of the layering system and reducing condensation without constraining body movement.
CLOSE
System Dual Protection
SDP was originally developed for use in Military applications, and has gone on to be used by Tactical Forces, Mountain Rescue and Emergency Services requiring performance clothing that works as hard as they do.
It has become a popular choice with the outdoor community and has been used to conquer the world’s toughest mountain summits and survive the harshest Arctic conditions.
In recognition of SDP’s success, Keela was awarded the Queen’s Award for Enterprise: Innovation, one of the UK’s most prestigious awards, which recognizes outstanding achievement in the categories of international trade, innovation and sustainable development. Keela are grateful for the recognition of their innovations and continue to further develop System Dual Protection to ensure our customers know they can face the elements with confidence and in comfort.
Just like condensation on a window or in your car, your jacket can build up moisture on the inside.
You’ve seen it before, you find your new jacket has moisture inside after a good half hour of physical exertion.
But why?
Although it may look and feel as though your jacket is letting in water, the moisture is in fact caused by condensation building up inside.
Think about your car windscreen on a cold day… fogging up due to the temperature difference between the inside and the outside  here force ventilation is needed to clear the moisture.
Just like that, no waterproof garments breathe in wet or old conditions, no matter what marketing hype may tell you. Breathability claims can be made, but with the international test standards being set in dry conditions at 21°C and above, the results are far removed from the conditions in which we expect our products to perform.
CLOSE
Sign up to our newsletter
Keep up to date with the latest news, special offers and newest products from Keela.
CLOSE
Keela Covid-19 Update
We appreciate the challenges of the current situation with COVID-19, but we remain fully operational for all orders and enquiries.
There may occasionally be a slight delay as we are prioritising emergency services orders, such as NHS, Ambulance, Police and other frontline services. We appreciate your understanding and patience in this situation – If you have any queries please email us at enquiries@keela.co.uk
CLOSE
Mens Lower Body Size Guide
CLOSE
Mens Upper Body Size Guide
CLOSE
Ladies Lower Body Size Guide
CLOSE
Ladies Upper Body Size Guide
CLOSE
Kids Size Guide
CLOSE
×
Accessories Size Guide
Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Sed eget dapibus lectus. Cras euismod vulputate eros. Nullam in condimentum sem. Ut a tellus magna. Curabitur id erat sed ex malesuada dictum vitae non velit. Cras vehicula fringilla posuere. Aliquam non tincidunt neque, eu ultrices arcu. Maecenas vel arcu sed felis ultrices imperdiet.
Morbi tincidunt, sapien et fringilla finibus, mi quam commodo orci, sed maximus sapien nunc quis dolor. Mauris odio sem, consequat at commodo sit amet, placerat sed lectus. Fusce ac elit id velit ornare dignissim eget non eros. Vestibulum porttitor at urna quis ultricies. Suspendisse odio erat, accumsan a lacinia quis, ullamcorper quis dolor. Praesent tempor magna nec lacus blandit, in molestie metus rhoncus. Maecenas eu porttitor ligula, id volutpat nisl.
CLOSE
This website uses cookies to provide you with the best browsing experience.Find out more or adjust your settings.
Accept
Close GDPR Cookie Settings
Privacy Overview
Strictly Necessary Cookies
Cookie Policy
Powered by  GDPR Cookie Compliance
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies so that we can provide you with the best user experience possible. Cookie information is stored in your browser and performs functions such as recognising you when you return to our website and helping our team to understand which sections of the website you find most interesting and useful.
Strictly Necessary Cookies
Strictly Necessary Cookie should be enabled at all times so that we can save your preferences for cookie settings.
Enable or Disable Cookies
If you disable this cookie, we will not be able to save your preferences. This means that every time you visit this website you will need to enable or disable cookies again.
Cookie Policy
More information about our Cookie Policy
Enable All
Save Settings
